This is the first ever allect electric
Ferrari. A car Ferrari said they'd never
make that will probably be the most
controversial car they've ever made, and
it's all because of this chart. In the
US, electric cars are only 10% of new
car sales and even starting to drop. But
in Europe, it's around 25%. And in
China, more than half of all new car
sales are electric cars and growing
fast. So Ferrari wants in. I'm at a
secret track in Italy to get a first
look before it launches. And the inside
is designed by Apple legend Johnny IV.
The guy who designed all of these iconic
screens, designed this car with fewer
screens and more physical buttons. But
the thing is, to make an electric
Ferrari, the Ferrari chief designer told
me you need a big battery. So this car
is bigger than you might expect. It's
the first ever five seat Ferrari. They
told me the real story behind why they
made this car. So to see it subscribe.